http://www.new-unity.org/data-privacy-notices

Home/
Community/Virtual Sunday GatheringsVirtual connection and supportVirtual discussionChristmas 2020Virtual helpingJusticeCharitiesDonateChildrenVolunteer
Leadership/MinisterTrusteesGovernanceTeams
Resources/TalksNewsLive streams
Spaces/Find usVenue hire: Upper StreetVenue hire: Newington GreenHistory: Upper StreetHistory: Newington GreenNewington Green Relaunch
Ceremonies/Virtual ceremonies
About/Non-religious ChurchStaffVacanciesContact us
Believe in good
Data privacy notices
Home/
Community/Virtual Sunday GatheringsVirtual connection and supportVirtual discussionChristmas 2020Virtual helpingJusticeCharitiesDonateChildrenVolunteer
Leadership/MinisterTrusteesGovernanceTeams
Resources/TalksNewsLive streams
Spaces/Find usVenue hire: Upper StreetVenue hire: Newington GreenHistory: Upper StreetHistory: Newington GreenNewington Green Relaunch
Ceremonies/Virtual ceremonies
About/Non-religious ChurchStaffVacanciesContact us
We have several data privacy notices here at New Unity.For our privacy notice covering New Unity’s role holders (including staff members, volunteers, ministers and trustees), click here.For our privacy notice covering renters who use our Upper Street building, click here.For our privacy notice covering renters who use our Newington Green building, click here.And for our notice covering congregants, click here.Please note: we record virtual Sunday Gatherings so that they can be viewed again later and so that segments can be used for promotion. Any re-use of recorded material will be without the Candles of Joys and Sorrows segment.
Home/
Community/Virtual Sunday GatheringsVirtual connection and supportVirtual discussionChristmas 2020Virtual helpingJusticeCharitiesDonateChildrenVolunteer
Leadership/MinisterTrusteesGovernanceTeams
Resources/TalksNewsLive streams
Spaces/Find usVenue hire: Upper StreetVenue hire: Newington GreenHistory: Upper StreetHistory: Newington GreenNewington Green Relaunch
Ceremonies/Virtual ceremonies
About/Non-religious ChurchStaffVacanciesContact us
New Unity
New Unity is an open-minded at radically-inclusive community. We're united in a belief that together we can effect positive change; both on a personal level and in the wider community.
What's a non-religious church? Start here!
Sign up to our newsletter!
Visit the website of our heritage project here!
Virtual Sunday Gatherings take place every week at 11:00 AM BST.
Join us!
Ask Andy anything
Ask Andy anything
Ask Andy anything!
Have a question? Ask anything and our minister, Andy Pakula, will email you a reply!
Your name
*
First Name
Last Name
Your email address
*
Needed so Andy can reply to you
Where do you live?
Not required. We're just curious!
Your question
*
Ask anything!
Thank you!
WEBSITE FEEDBACK
Hire our Space
Thank you for visiting New Unity’s website! We’d love to welcome you to one of our events soon.New Unity CIORegistered Charity No. 1161363Copyright © 2020 New Unity CIO
Data privacy noticesPolicies and guidelinesFind usContact us
